<resources>
    <string name="app_name">v3 Tour Guide App (Welcome To Rome!)</string>
    <string name="item_image">Image Of Item</string>
    <string name="see_fragment">See</string>
    <string name="eat_fragment">Eat</string>
    <string name="sleep_fragment">Sleep</string>
    <string name="tour_fragment">Tours</string>
    <string name="colosseum_name">Colosseum</string>
    <string name="colosseum_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazza del Colosseo, 1, 00184 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="colosseum_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 39967700</string>
    <string name="colosseum_hours">HOURS:\nEveryday 8:30am - 7:00pm</string>
    <string name="colosseum_description">ABOUT:\nThe Colosseum or Coliseum, also known as the Flavian Amphitheatre,
        is an oval amphitheatre in the centre of the city of Rome, Italy. Built of travertine, tuff,
        and brick-faced concrete, it is the largest amphitheatre ever built.  The Colosseum was used
        for gladiatorial contests and various public spectacles such as mock sea battles, animal hunts,
        executions, re-enactments of famous battles, and dramas based on Classical mythology.</string>
    <string name="roman_forum_name">Roman Forum</string>
    <string name="roman_forum_address">ADDRESS:\nVia della Salara Vecchia, 5/6, 00186 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="roman_forum_phone">ADDRESS:\n+39 06 0608</string>
    <string name="roman_forum_hours">HOURS:\nEveryday 9:00am - 7:00pm</string>
    <string name="roman_forum_description">ABOUT:\nThe Roman Forum, is a rectangular forum (plaza) surrounded
        by the ruins of several important ancient government buildings at the center of the city of Rome.
        Citizens of the ancient city referred to this space, originally a marketplace, as the Forum Magnum,
        or simply the Forum. For centuries the Forum was the center of day-to-day life in Rome: the site
        of triumphal processions and elections; the venue for public speeches, criminal trials, and
        gladiatorial matches; and the nucleus of commercial affairs.  The Forum today is a sprawling
        ruin of architectural fragments and intermittent archaeological excavations.</string>
    <string name="arch_constantine_name">Arch of Constantine</string>
    <string name="arch_constantine_address">ADDRESS:\nVia di San Gregorio, 00186 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="arch_constantine_phone">ADDRESS:\n+39 06 0606</string>
    <string name="arch_constantine_hours">HOURS:\nOpen 24 Hours</string>
    <string name="arch_constantine_description">ABOUT:\nThe Arch of Constantine is a triumphal arch in Rome,
        situated between the Colosseum and the Palatine Hill. It was erected by the Roman Senate to
        commemorate Constantine I\'s victory over Maxentius at the Battle of Milvian Bridge in 312.
        Dedicated in 315, it is the largest Roman triumphal arch. The arch spans the Via triumphalis,
        the way taken by the emperors when they entered the city in triumph.</string>
    <string name="arch_titus_name">Arch of Titus</string>
    <string name="arch_titus_address">ADDRESS:\nVia Sacra, 00186 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="arch_titus_phone">PHONE:\nNo Phone Number</string>
    <string name="arch_titus_hours">HOURS:\nOpen 24 Hours</string>
    <string name="arch_titus_description">ABOUT:\nThe Arch of Titus is a 1st-century AD honorific arch,
        located on the Via Sacra, Rome, just to the south-east of the Roman Forum. It was constructed
        in c. AD 82 by the Emperor Domitian shortly after the death of his older brother Titus to
        commemorate Titus\'s victories. The arch has provided the general model for many triumphal
        arches erected since the 16th century - perhaps most famously it is the inspiration for the
        Arc de Triomphe in Paris, France.</string>
    <string name="palatine_hill_name">Palatine Hill</string>
    <string name="palatine_hill_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazza Santa Maria Nova, 53, 00186 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="palatine_hill_phone">PHONE:\n+39.06.39967700</string>
    <string name="palatine_hill_hours">HOURS:\nEveryday 8.30am to one hour before sunset</string>
    <string name="palatine_hill_description">ABOUT:\nThe Palatine Hill is the centremost of the Seven Hills
        of Rome and is one of the most ancient parts of the city. It stands 40 metres above the Roman
        Forum, looking down upon it on one side, and upon the Circus Maximus on the other. From the
        time of Augustus Imperial palaces were built here. The hill is the etymological origin of the
        word palace and its cognates in other languages (Italian: palazzo, French: palais, German: Palast, etc.).</string>
    <string name="circus_maximus_name">Circus Maximus</string>
    <string name="circus_maximus_address">ADDRESS:\nVia del Circo Massimo, 00186 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="circus_maximus_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 0608</string>
    <string name="circus_maximus_hours">HOURS:\nOpen 24 Hours</string>
    <string name="circus_maximus_description">ABOUT:\nThe Circus Maximus is an ancient Roman chariot-racing
        stadium and mass entertainment venue located in Rome, Italy. Situated in the valley between
        the Aventine and Palatine Hills, it was the first and largest stadium in ancient Rome and its
        later Empire. It measured 621 m (2,037 ft) in length and 118 m (387 ft) in width and could
        accommodate over 150,000 spectators. In its fully developed form, it became the model for circuses
        throughout the Roman Empire. The site is now a public park.</string>
    <string name="capitoline_museums_name">Capitoline Museums</string>
    <string name="capitoline_museums_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazza del Campidoglio, 1, 00186 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="capitoline_museums_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 0608</string>
    <string name="capitoline_museums_hours">HOURS:\nEveryday 9:30am - 7:30pm</string>
    <string name="capitoline_museums_description">ABOUT:\nThe Capitoline Museums are a single museum containing
        a group of art and archaeological museums in Piazza del Campidoglio, on top of the Capitoline Hill
        in Rome, Italy.  It opened to the public in 1734 under Clement XII, the Capitoline Museums are
        considered the first museum in the world, understood as a place where art could be enjoyed by
        all and not only by the owners.</string>
    <string name="capitoline_hill_name">Capitoline Hill</string>
    <string name="capitoline_hill_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazza del Campidoglio, 00186 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="capitoline_hill_phone">PHONE:\nNo Phone Number</string>
    <string name="capitoline_hill_hours">HOURS:\nOpen 24 Hours</string>
    <string name="capitoline_hill_description">ABOUT:\nThe Capitoline Hill between the Forum and the Campus
        Martius, is one of the Seven Hills of Rome. The Capitolium (as it became known) was regarded
        by the Romans as indestructible, and was adopted as a symbol of eternity.  The Capitoline Hill
        contains few ancient ground-level ruins, as they are almost entirely covered up by Medieval
        and Renaissance palaces (now housing the Capitoline Museums) that surround a piazza, a significant
        urban plan designed by famous sculpture, painter, architect, and poet - Michelangelo.</string>
    <string name="altare_della_patria_name">Altare della Patria</string>
    <string name="altare_della_patria_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazza Venezia, 00186 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="altare_della_patria_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 678 0664</string>
    <string name="altare_della_patria_hours">HOURS:\nEveryday 9:00am - 7:00pm</string>
    <string name="altare_della_patria_description">ABOUT:\nThe Altare della Patria (English: \"Altar of the Fatherland\"),
        also known as the Monumento Nazionale a Vittorio Emanuele II (\"National Monument to Victor Emmanuel II\")
        or Il Vittoriano, is a monument built in honor of Victor Emmanuel, the first king of a unified Italy,
        located in Rome, Italy. It occupies a site between the Piazza Venezia and the Capitoline Hill.
        The Vittoriano features stairways, Corinthian columns, fountains, an equestrian sculpture of
        Victor Emmanuel and two statues of the goddess Victoria riding on quadrigas. The base of the
        structure houses the museum of Italian Unification.</string>
    <string name="trajans_column_name">Trajan\'s Column</string>
    <string name="trajans_column_address">ADDRESS:\nVia dei Fori Imperiali, 00187 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="trajans_column_phone">PHONE:\nNo Phone Number</string>
    <string name="trajans_column_hours">HOURS:\nOpen 24 Hours</string>
    <string name="trajans_column_description">ABOUT:\nTrajan\'s Column is a Roman triumphal column in Rome, Italy,
        that commemorates Roman emperor Trajan\'s victory in the Dacian Wars.  It is located in Trajan\'s
        Forum, north of the Roman Forum. Completed in AD 113, the freestanding column is most famous for
        its spiral bas relief, which artistically represents the wars between the Romans and Dacians
        (101–102 and 105–106). Its design has inspired numerous victory columns, both ancient and modern.</string>
    <string name="trajans_market_name">Trajan\'s Market</string>
    <string name="trajans_market_address">ADDRESS:\nVia Quattro Novembre, 94, 00187 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="trajans_market_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 0608</string>
    <string name="trajans_market_hours">HOURS:\nEveryday 9:30am - 7:30pm</string>
    <string name="trajans_market_description">ABOUT:\nTrajan\'s Market is a large complex of ruins in the city
        of Rome, Italy. Located on the Via dei Fori Imperiali, at the opposite end to the Colosseum.
        Thought to be the world\'s oldest shopping mall, the arcades in Trajan\'s Market are now believed
        by many to be administrative offices for Emperor Trajan. The shops and apartments were built
        in a multi-level structure and it is still possible to visit several of the levels. Highlights
        include delicate marble floors and the remains of a library.</string>
    <string name="basilica_maggiore_name">Basilica Papale di Santa Maria Maggiore</string>
    <string name="basilica_maggiore_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazza di S. Maria Maggiore, 42, 00100 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="basilica_maggiore_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 6988 6800</string>
    <string name="basilica_maggiore_hours">HOURS:\nEveryday 7:00am - 7:00pm</string>
    <string name="basilica_maggiore_description">ABOUT:\nThe Basilica di Santa Maria Maggiore or church of
        Santa Maria Maggiore, is a Papal major basilica and the largest Catholic Marian church in Rome, Italy.
        The basilica enshrines the venerated image of Salus Populi Romani, depicting the Blessed Virgin
        Mary as the help and protectress of the Roman people, which was granted a Canonical coronation
        by Pope Gregory XVI on 15 August 1838 accompanied by his Papal bull Cælestis Regina.</string>
    <string name="trevi_fountain_name">Trevi Fountain</string>
    <string name="trevi_fountain_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazza di Trevi, 00187 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="trevi_fountain_phone">PHONE:\nNo Phone Number</string>
    <string name="trevi_fountain_hours">HOURS:\nOpen 24 hours</string>
    <string name="trevi_fountain_description">ABOUT:\nThe Trevi Fountain is a fountain in the Trevi district
        in Rome, Italy, designed by Italian architect Nicola Salvi and completed by Giuseppe Pannini.
        Standing 26.3 metres (86 ft) high and 49.15 metres (161.3 ft) wide, it is the largest Baroque
        fountain in the city and one of the most famous fountains in the world. The fountain has appeared
        in several notable films, including Federico Fellini\'s "La Dolce Vita", the eponymous
        \"Three Coins in the Fountain\", and \"Roman Holiday\".</string>
    <string name="pantheon_name">Pantheon</string>
    <string name="pantheon_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazza della Rotonda, 00186 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="pantheon_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 6830 0230</string>
    <string name="pantheon_hours">HOURS:\nMonday - Saturday 9:00am - 6:00pm\nSunday 8:30am - 7:30pm</string>
    <string name="pantheon_description">ABOUT:\nThe Pantheon (from the Greek: Pantheion, \"[temple] of all the gods\")
        is a former Roman temple, now a church, in Rome, Italy, on the site of an earlier temple commissioned
        by Marcus Agrippa during the reign of Augustus (27 BC - 14 AD). It was completed by the emperor
        Hadrian and probably dedicated around 126 AD. Its date of construction is uncertain, because
        Hadrian chose not to inscribe the new temple but rather to retain the inscription of Agrippa\'s
        older temple, which had burned down.</string>
    <string name="fontana_quattro_fiumi_name">Fontana dei Quattro Fiumi</string>
    <string name="fontana_quattro_fiumi_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazza Navona, 00186 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="fontana_quattro_fiumi_phone">PHONE:\nNo Phone Number</string>
    <string name="fontana_quattro_fiumi_hours">HOURS:\nOpen 24 hours</string>
    <string name="fontana_quattro_fiumi_description">ABOUT:\nFontana dei Quattro Fiumi (Fountain of the Four
        Rivers) is a fountain in the Piazza Navona in Rome, Italy. It was designed in 1651 by Gian
        Lorenzo Bernini for Pope Innocent X whose family palace, the Palazzo Pamphili, faced onto the
        piazza as did the church of Sant\'Agnese in Agone of which Innocent was the sponsor.</string>
    <string name="piazza_navona_name">Piazza Navona</string>
    <string name="piazza_navona_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazza Navona, 00186 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="piazza_navona_phone">PHONE:\nNo Phone Number</string>
    <string name="piazza_navona_hours">HOURS:\nOpen 24 hours</string>
    <string name="piazza_navona_description">ABOUT:\nPiazza Navona is a square in Rome, Italy. It is built on
        the site of the Stadium of Domitian, built in the 1st century AD, and follows the form of the
        open space of the stadium. The ancient Romans went there to watch the agones (games), and
        hence it was known as \"Circus Agonalis\" (\"Competition Arena\"). It is believed that over time
        the name changed to \"in avone\" then to \"navone\" and eventually to \"navona\".</string>
    <string name="castel_sant_angelo_name">Castel Sant\'Angelo</string>
    <string name="castel_sant_angelo_address">ADDRESS:\nLungotevere Castello, 50, 00193 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="castel_sant_angelo_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 32810</string>
    <string name="castel_sant_angelo_hours">HOURS:\nEveryday 9:00am - 7:30pm</string>
    <string name="castel_sant_angelo_description">ABOUT:\nThe Mausoleum of Hadrian, usually known as Castel
        Sant\'Angelo (Castle of the Holy Angel), is a towering cylindrical building in Parco Adriano,
        Rome, Italy. It was initially commissioned by the Roman Emperor Hadrian as a mausoleum for
        himself and his family. The building was later used by the popes as a fortress and castle,
        and is now a museum. The structure was once the tallest building in Rome.</string>
    <string name="st_peter_square_name">St. Peter\'s Square</string>
    <string name="st_peter_square_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazza San Pietro, 00120 Città del Vaticano, Vatican City</string>
    <string name="st_peter_square_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 6988 1840</string>
    <string name="st_peter_square_hours">HOURS:\nOpen 24 Hours</string>
    <string name="st_peter_square_description">ABOUT:\nSt. Peter\'s Square is a large plaza located directly
        in front of St. Peter\'s Basilica in the Vatican City, the papal enclave inside Rome,
        directly west of the neighbourhood or rione of Borgo. Both the square and the basilica are
        named after Saint Peter, an apostle of Jesus and the first Catholic Pope. At the centre of
        the square there is an ancient Egyptian obelisk, erected at the current site in 1586.</string>
    <string name="st_peter_basilica_name">St. Peter\'s Basilica</string>
    <string name="st_peter_basilica_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazza San Pietro, 00120 Città del Vaticano, Vatican City</string>
    <string name="st_peter_basilica_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 6988 3731</string>
    <string name="st_peter_basilica_hours">HOURS:\nEveryday 7:00am - 6:30pm</string>
    <string name="st_peter_basilica_description">ABOUT:\nThe Papal Basilica of St. Peter in the Vatican or simply
        St. Peter\'s Basilica is an Italian Renaissance church in Vatican City, the papal enclave within
        the city of Rome. Designed principally by Donato Bramante, Michelangelo, Carlo Maderno and
        Gian Lorenzo Bernini, St. Peter\'s is the most renowned work of Renaissance architecture and
        the largest church in the world. While it is neither the mother church of the Catholic Church
        nor the cathedral of the Diocese of Rome, St. Peter\'s is regarded as one of the holiest Catholic shrines.</string>
    <string name="sistine_chapel_name">Sistine Chapel</string>
    <string name="sistine_chapel_address">ADDRESS:\nCitta del Vaticano 1, 00120 Vatican City, Italy</string>
    <string name="sistine_chapel_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 6988 4676</string>
    <string name="sistine_chapel_hours">HOURS:\nMonday - Saturday 9:00am - 4:00pm\nSunday Closed</string>
    <string name="sistine_chapel_description">ABOUT:\nThe Sistine Chapel is a chapel in the Apostolic Palace,
        the official residence of the Pope, in Vatican City. Originally known as the Cappella Magna,
        the chapel takes its name from Pope Sixtus IV, who restored it between 1477 and 1480. Since
        that time, the chapel has served as a place of both religious and functionary papal activity.
        Today it is the site of the Papal conclave, the process by which a new pope is selected. The
        fame of the Sistine Chapel lies mainly in the frescos that decorate the interior, and most
        particularly the Sistine Chapel ceiling and The Last Judgment by Michelangelo.</string>
    <string name="vatican_museums_name">Vatican Museums</string>
    <string name="vatican_museums_address">ADDRESS:\nViale Vaticano, 00120 Vatican City, Italy</string>
    <string name="vatican_museums_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 69884676</string>
    <string name="vatican_museums_hours">HOURS:\nMonday - Saturday 9:00am - 6:00pm\nEvery Last Sunday
        Of The Month 9:00am - 2:00pm</string>
    <string name="vatican_museums_description">ABOUT:\nThe Vatican Museums are Christian and art museums
        located within the city boundaries of the Vatican City. They display works from the immense
        collection amassed by Popes throughout the centuries including some of the most renowned
        classical sculptures and most important masterpieces of Renaissance art in the world. The
        museums contain roughly 70,000 works, of which 20,000 are on display, and currently employ
        640 people who work in 40 different administrative, scholarly, and restoration departments.</string>
    <string name="spanish_steps_name">Spanish Steps</string>
    <string name="spanish_steps_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazza di Spagna, 00187 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="spanish_steps_phone">PHONE:\n+39 090 8388 1200</string>
    <string name="spanish_steps_hours">HOURS:\nOpen 24 Hours</string>
    <string name="spanish_steps_description">ABOUT:\nThe Spanish Steps are a set of steps in Rome, Italy,
        climbing a steep slope between the Piazza di Spagna at the base and Piazza Trinità dei Monti,
        dominated by the Trinità dei Monti church at the top. The monumental stairway of 135 steps
        (the slightly elevated drainage system is often mistaken for the first step) was built with
        French diplomat Étienne Gueffier’s bequeathed funds of 20,000 scudi, in 1723–1725.</string>
    <string name="galleria_borghese_name">Galleria Borghese</string>
    <string name="galleria_borghese_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazzale Scipione Borghese, 5, 00197 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="galleria_borghese_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 32810</string>
    <string name="galleria_borghese_hours">HOURS:\nTuesday - Sunday 9:00am - 7:00pm\nMonday Closed</string>
    <string name="galleria_borghese_description">ABOUT:\nThe Galleria Borghese (Borghese Gallery) is an art
        gallery in Rome, Italy, housed in the former Villa Borghese Pinciana. At the outset, the
        gallery building was integrated with its gardens, but today, the Villa Borghese gardens are
        considered a separate tourist attraction. The Galleria Borghese houses a substantial part of
        the Borghese collection of paintings, sculpture and antiquities, begun by Cardinal Scipione
        Borghese, the nephew of Pope Paul V. The Villa was built by the architect Flaminio Ponzio,
        developing sketches by Scipione Borghese himself, who used it as a villa suburbana, a country
        villa at the edge of Rome.</string>
    <string name="piazza_del_popolo_name">Piazza del Popolo</string>
    <string name="piazza_del_popolo_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazza del Popolo, 00187 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="piazza_del_popolo_phone">PHONE:\nNo Phone Number</string>
    <string name="piazza_del_popolo_hours">HOURS:\nOpen 24 Hours</string>
    <string name="piazza_del_popolo_description">ABOUT:\nPiazza del Popolo is a large urban square in Rome.
        The name in modern Italian literally means \"People\'s Square\", but historically it derives
        from the poplars after which the church of Santa Maria del Popolo, in the northeast corner
        of the piazza, takes its name. The piazza lies inside the northern gate in the Aurelian Walls,
        once the Porta Flaminia of ancient Rome, and now called the Porta del Popolo. This was the
        traveller\'s first view of Rome upon arrival. For centuries, the Piazza del Popolo was a place
        for public executions, the last of which took place in 1826.</string>
    <string name="ristorante_pepe_rosa_name">Ristorante Pepe Rosa</string>
    <string name="ristorante_pepe_rosa_address">ADDRESS:\nVia Degli Orti di Cesare &#8531; | Near
        Stazione Trastevere, 00153 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="ristorante_pepe_rosa_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 6941 2532</string>
    <string name="ristorante_pepe_rosa_hours">HOURS:\nMonday Closed\nTuesday - Thursday 12:00pm - 3:00pm
        and 7:00pm - 10:30pm\nFriday - Sunday 12:00pm - 3:00pm and 7:00pm - 11:00pm</string>
    <string name="ristorante_pepe_rosa_description">ABOUT:\nCasareccia cuisine in an intimate and welcoming
        atmosphere near Trastevere station. Staff young, friendly and helpful to your requests.
        Traditional Roman cuisine and other specialities await you.</string>
    <string name="il_tamburello_pulcinella_name">Il Tamburello di Pulcinella</string>
    <string name="il_tamburello_pulcinella_address">ADDRESS:\nVia Pasquale Fiore 23, 00165 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="il_tamburello_pulcinella_phone">PHONE:\n+39 329 285 1794</string>
    <string name="il_tamburello_pulcinella_hours">HOURS:\nTuesday - Sunday 7:00pm - 12:00am\nMonday Closed</string>
    <string name="il_tamburello_pulcinella_description">ABOUT:\nThe Tamburelli specialties are unique and original
        dishes. The best of Campanian and Mediterranean cuisine, revisited by the aged chef Corrado
        Talamo, award-winning, with over 40 years of experience and some successful books to his credit,
        such as the encyclopedic book, \"La Storia della Cucina\", also downloadable online.</string>
    <string name="tonnarello_name">Tonnarello</string>
    <string name="tonnarello_address">ADDRESS:\nVia della Paglia 1, 00153 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="tonnarello_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 580 6404</string>
    <string name="tonnarello_hours">HOURS:\nEveryday 8:00am - 12:00am</string>
    <string name="tonnarello_description">ABOUT:\nWe are in the heart of the Roman tradition, in the center
        of culture, at the highest density point of the capital\'s restaurants. This is why we must
        be head and shoulders above the rest in our sector. We offer you Roman dishes at their best, a
        staff at your disposal that will always welcome you with a smile and all the space of our 5
        rooms at your disposal. Each ingredient is carefully selected, the presentation of our dishes is never
        left to chance, and our staff in the room are trained to give you the best of experiences.
        We do not talk about Tiramisù, you have to come and taste it.</string>
    <string name="burger_bistrot_name">Burger Bistrot</string>
    <string name="burger_bistrot_address">ADDRESS:\nVia Cavour 291, 00184 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="burger_bistrot_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 487 4461</string>
    <string name="burger_bistrot_hours">HOURS:\nMonday - Thursday 12:00pm - 3:00pm and 6:00pm - 10:00pm\n
        Friday - Sunday 12:00pm - 10:00pm</string>
    <string name="burger_bistrot_description">ABOUT:\nBurger Bistrot was born in October 2017 from the idea
        of ​​two Roman boys with the intent to bring innovation into one of the most eaten dishes in the
        world. We are the first \"hamburgeria\" in Rome where you can eat a hamburger cooked in a vacuum,
        a process that makes it juicy and never dry.</string>
    <string name="mimi_e_coco_name">Mimi e Coco</string>
    <string name="mimi_e_coco_address">ADDRESS:\nVia del Governo Vecchio 72, 00186 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="mimi_e_coco_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 6821 0845</string>
    <string name="mimi_e_coco_hours">HOURS:\nEveryday 9:00am - 2:00am</string>
    <string name="mimi_e_coco_description">ABOUT:\nRight in the heart of Rome, there\'s a place where the sun
        always shines. It\'s where you can find us. Cosy and inviting, located in what was once a
        16th century Bishop\'s Palace, ours is the perfect location for anyone who wants to relish
        an easy going and comfortable mood on the set of Rome\'s bustling nightlife. With a vas
        assortment of wines, a special eye to Italian ones, you can find platters of cold meats
        and cheese or traditional dishes such as carbonara or straccetti. You can also enjoy a
        Traminer with a Pizza Margherita, a fresh mixed salad and our hallmark crostini of potatoes
        with a choice of \"provola cheese and vegetables\" or \"speck and porcini mushrooms\"! To finish
        with style you can try our yummy Illy Tiramisù served warm and made on the spot for you.</string>
    <string name="cantina_e_cucina_name">Cantina e Cucina</string>
    <string name="cantina_e_cucina_address">ADDRESS:\nVia del Governo Vecchio 87, 00186 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="cantina_e_cucina_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 689 2574</string>
    <string name="cantina_e_cucina_hours">HOURS:\nMonday - Saturday 7:00am - 2:00am\nSunday 8:00am - 2:00am</string>
    <string name="cantina_e_cucina_description">ABOUT:\nEating is an emotional experience. We take care to
        create the best atmosphere, with staff that takes care of you to make you feel at home. Our
        cooks and pizza makers are accustomed to a high level of attention to detail, with food cooked
        specifically for you. Your satisfaction is all we crave. A good meal is not just something
        that fills the stomach, but something pleasant that should never be forgotten.</string>
    <string name="arrosticino_pane_vino_name">Arrosticino Pane and Vino</string>
    <string name="arrosticino_pane_vino_address">ADDRESS:\nVia Selinunte 59,61, 00174 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="arrosticino_pane_vino_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 9978 2715</string>
    <string name="arrosticino_pane_vino_hours">HOURS:\nTuesday - Sunday 7:00pm - 11:45pm\nMonday Closed</string>
    <string name="arrosticino_pane_vino_description">ABOUT:\nServing a good selection of Italian, barbecue
        and gluten free options.  It\'s a great place for local cuisine, special occasions, large
        groups and families with children.</string>
    <string name="alchimia_foodlab_name">Alchimia Foodlab</string>
    <string name="alchimia_foodlab_address">ADDRESS:\nVia Vercelli 6, 00182 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="alchimia_foodlab_phone">PHONE:\n+39 366 207 7143</string>
    <string name="alchimia_foodlab_hours">HOURS:\nMonday 7:00pm - 10:30pm\nTuesday - Friday 12:30pm - 3:30pm and
        7:00pm - 10:30pm\nSaturday 9:00am - 10:30pm\nSunday Closed</string>
    <string name="alchimia_foodlab_description">ABOUT:\nAs Alchemists create gold, we transform the raw material
        to create healthy dishes and haute cuisine, in a quick and practical solution to be consumed
        on the street, at work or at home.  We serve a great selection of Italian, seafood, European,
        healthy, street food, mediterranean, vegetarian friendly, vegan options and gluten free options.</string>
    <string name="osti_matti_name">Osti Matti</string>
    <string name="osti_matti_address">ADDRESS:\nVia Assisi 11/A, 00181 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="osti_matti_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 7839 3610</string>
    <string name="osti_matti_hours">HOURS:\nMonday - Friday 7:30pm - 10:30pm\nSaturday - Sunday 12:30pm - 2:30pm and
        7:30pm - 10:30pm</string>
    <string name="osti_matti_description">ABOUT:\nBefore being a trattoria, Osti Matti wants to be a project
        to rediscover ancient flavors. Passion, love and care, this is the starting point for all
        great meals.  Osti Matti is a great dining location for families with children, special
        occasions, romantic nights out and local cuisine.</string>
    <string name="the_loft_name">The Loft</string>
    <string name="the_loft_address">ADDRESS:\nVia Leone IV 34 | Intersection with Via Giulio Cesare, 00192 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="the_loft_phone">PHONE:\n+39 347 004 5169</string>
    <string name="the_loft_hours">HOURS:\nEveryday 7:00am - 2:00am\nExcept Tuesday and Thursday 7:00am - 12:00am</string>
    <string name="the_loft_description">ABOUT:\nFamily friendly restaurant serving Italian, brew pub, fast food,
        cafe, Mediterranean, European, vegetarian, vegan and gluten free options.</string>
    <string name="otello_name">Otello</string>
    <string name="otello_address">ADDRESS:\nVia della Pelliccia 47/53 | Trastevere, 00153 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="otello_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 589 6848</string>
    <string name="otello_hours">HOURS:\nEveryday 11:00am - 1:00am</string>
    <string name="otello_description">ABOUT:\nFamily friendly restaurant that also accommodates large groups.
        Serving a great selection of Italian, vegetarian, vegan and gluten free food choices.</string>
    <string name="armando_al_pantheon_name">Armando al Pantheon</string>
    <string name="armando_al_pantheon_address">ADDRESS:\nSalita dei Crescenzi, 31, 00186 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="armando_al_pantheon_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 6880 3034</string>
    <string name="armando_al_pantheon_hours">HOURS:\nMonday - Saturday 12:30pm - 2:45pm and 7:00pm - 11:00pm\n
        Sunday Closed</string>
    <string name="armando_al_pantheon_description">ABOUT:\nA long-standing family friendly restaurant serving
        hearty, traditional Roman fare in a wood-paneled dining room. Vegetarian and gluten free
        options are available as well.</string>
    <string name="palazzo_manfredi_name">Palazzo Manfredi</string>
    <string name="palazzo_manfredi_address">ADDRESS:\nVia Labicana, 125, Rome, RM, 00184, Italy</string>
    <string name="palazzo_manfredi_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 77591380</string>
    <string name="palazzo_manfredi_website">WEBSITE:\nhttps://www.palazzomanfredi.com</string>
    <string name="palazzo_manfredi_description">ABOUT:\n5 Star Hotel - Palazzo Manfredi is a magnificent
        historic villa that today serves as five-star hotel offering the tradition and warm hospitality
        of the Counts Manfredi. Every detail is a family jewel, from the spectacular view of the
        Colosseum, to the courtesy of our staff, the classic and contemporary elegance of the decor,
        and our sophisticated restaurant on one of Rome\'s most romantic terraces. History is on our
        doorstep, but true luxury is being part of a great family\'s history.</string>
    <string name="palazzo_montemartini_name">Palazzo Montemartini</string>
    <string name="palazzo_montemartini_address">ADDRESS:\nLargo Giovanni Montemartini 20, 00185 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="palazzo_montemartini_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 45661</string>
    <string name="palazzo_montemartini_website">WEBSITE:\nhttp://www.palazzomontemartini.com</string>
    <string name="palazzo_montemartini_description">ABOUT:\n5 Star Hotel - Palazzo Montemartini is a 3-minute
        walk from the nearest metro station, this contemporary hotel in a stately former palazzo is a
        minute\'s stroll from the National Roman Museum\'s Baths of Diocletian. Individually decorated
        rooms feature hardwood floors and chic furnishings, and include flat-screen TVs, free Wi-Fi and
        minibars. Distinctive touches in individual suites include private spas, fitness equipment and
        lounges, as well as terraces with scenic city views.</string>
    <string name="iq_hotel_roma_name">iQ Hotel Roma</string>
    <string name="iq_hotel_roma_address">ADDRESS:\nVia Firenze, 8, 00184 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="iq_hotel_roma_phone">PHONE:\n011 39 06 9480 7545</string>
    <string name="iq_hotel_roma_website">WEBSITE:\nhttps://www.iqhotelroma.it</string>
    <string name="iq_hotel_roma_description">ABOUT:\nIQ Hotel Roma is a 4 star hotel, with a twist! Located
        in downtown Rome, just a short 15 minute walk from the Trevi Fountain or the Colosseum and
        with Repubblica metro station just 200 metres away, hotels don\'t get much more central than this.
        IQ guests enjoy free Wi-Fi connection throughout the hotel, a lovely terrace to unwind while
        overlooking the Opera House, and free access to our gym and sauna. IQ offers very competitive
        prices. Now that you\'ve found us, welcome to a whole new hotel experience!</string>
    <string name="voi_donna_camilla_savelli_name">VOI Donna Camilla Savelli</string>
    <string name="voi_donna_camilla_savelli_address">ADDRESS:\nVia Garibaldi 27, 98043 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="voi_donna_camilla_savelli_phone">PHONE:\n011 39 06 588861</string>
    <string name="voi_donna_camilla_savelli_website">WEBSITE:\nhttps://www.voihotels.com</string>
    <string name="voi_donna_camilla_savelli_description">ABOUT:\n4 Star Hotel - VOI Donna Camilla Savelli is
        set in a converted 17th-century convent in the Trastevere district, this refined hotel lies
        a minute\'s walk from a bus stop, 2.4 km from the Sistine Chapel and 2.9 km from the Colosseum.
        Featuring tile floors, the elegant rooms include free Wi-Fi, flat-screen TVs and minibars. Room
        service is available. Upgraded rooms feature antique furniture, while suites add separate living
        areas. The hotel provides complimentary, American-style breakfast.</string>
    <string name="britannia_hotel_name">The Britannia Hotel</string>
    <string name="britannia_hotel_address">ADDRESS:\nVia Napoli 64, 00184 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="britannia_hotel_phone">PHONE:\n011 39 06 9480 7071</string>
    <string name="britannia_hotel_website">WEBSITE:\nhttp://www.maghotels.it/ita/the-britannia-hotel/index.html</string>
    <string name="britannia_hotel_description">ABOUT:\n4 Star Hotel - The Britannia Hotel is in the centre of
        Rome, only 200 meters from the Teatro dell\'Opera opera house and the Repubblica metro station.
        An elegant nineteenth century building houses The Britannia Hotel, a refined boutique hotel
        with a particularly British atmosphere. These intimate and elegant chambers are equipped with
        top quality linen, private bathrooms with spacious showers or baths, satellite TV with LCD
        screens, a free high-speed Wi-Fi internet connection, a safe, an ironing board and a UV sun
        lamp. We also offer guests a selection of free items in the mini-bar upon arrival.</string>
    <string name="hotel_santa_maria_name">Hotel Santa Maria</string>
    <string name="hotel_santa_maria_address">ADDRESS:\nVicolo del Piede 2, 00153 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="hotel_santa_maria_phone">PHONE:\n011 39 06 589 4626</string>
    <string name="hotel_santa_maria_website">WEBSITE:\nhttps://www.hotelsantamariatrastevere.it</string>
    <string name="hotel_santa_maria_description">ABOUT:\n3 Star Hotel - Hotel Santa Maria was awarded the
        Certificate of Excellence and ranked in the top 10 hotels in Rome by TripAdvisor. The Hotel
        Santa Maria Rome is situated in the charming district of Trastevere. Consistently rated by
        guests as a fantastic hotel which offers excellent value for money. The Hotel Santa Maria is
        situated in a completely renovated 16th Century cloister offering 19 comfortable rooms and
        positioned within walking distance of the major archaeological and tourist sites of Rome.</string>
    <string name="cardilli_luxury_rooms_name">Cardilli Luxury Rooms</string>
    <string name="cardilli_luxury_rooms_address">ADDRESS:\nVia Milano 49, 00184 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="cardilli_luxury_rooms_phone">PHONE:\n011 39 0773 198 0042</string>
    <string name="cardilli_luxury_rooms_website">WEBSITE:\nhttp://www.bbromacardilli.com</string>
    <string name="cardilli_luxury_rooms_description">ABOUT:\n4 Star Hotel - Cardilli Luxury Rooms is a 7-minute
        walk from the nearest metro stop. This intimate hotel in Rome\'s historic center lies 1.1 km
        from the Roman Forum and 1.3 km from the Colosseum.  Refined rooms and suites with soundproof
        windows, private bathrooms, free Wi-Fi, TVs and minibars. Suites add separate sitting
        areas. Room service is offered. Free breakfast is served in an elegant dining room. Pets are welcome.</string>
    <string name="martis_palace_hotel_name">Martis Palace Hotel Rome</string>
    <string name="martis_palace_hotel_address">ADDRESS:\nVia San Giuseppe Calasanzio 1, 00186 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="martis_palace_hotel_phone">PHONE:\n011 39 06 9480 8158</string>
    <string name="martis_palace_hotel_website">WEBSITE:\nhttps://www.hotelmartis.com</string>
    <string name="martis_palace_hotel_description">ABOUT:\n4 Star Hotel - Martis Palace Hotel Rome is in a
        stately neoclassical building surrounded by shops and eateries. This polished hotel is a
        3-minute walk from Piazza Navona, a landmark square with fountains, and 3 km from Termini
        train station.  Warmly furnished rooms have free Wi-Fi and flat-screen TVs, as well as minibars
        and laptop-sized safes. Elegant suites add sitting areas; some include 4-poster beds. Other
        amenities include a rooftop terrace and a sophisticated guest lounge.</string>
    <string name="campo_marzio_luxury_suites_name">Campo Marzio Luxury Suites</string>
    <string name="campo_marzio_luxury_suites_address">ADDRESS:\nVia di Campo Marzio 52/a, Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="campo_marzio_luxury_suites_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 8767 9475</string>
    <string name="campo_marzio_luxury_suites_website">WEBSITE:\nhttp://www.suites4rome.com</string>
    <string name="campo_marzio_luxury_suites_description">ABOUT:\n4 Star Hotel - Campo Marzio Luxury Suites
        is in an historic building on a cobblestone street. This polished hotel is an 8-minute walk
        from both the Trevi Fountain and Piazza Navona. It\'s 2 km from Roma Termini train station.
        Warm, understated rooms and suites come with complimentary Wi-Fi, flat-screen TVs and minibars;
        some add exposed brick walls. An upgraded suite has a sitting area and a free-standing tub.
        In-room continental breakfast is included.Parking is offered for a fee.</string>
    <string name="mamas_home_name">Mama\'s Home Rome</string>
    <string name="mamas_home_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazza Campo de\' Fiori, 27, 00186 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="mamas_home_phone">PHONE:\n+39 335 437 211</string>
    <string name="mamas_home_website">WEBSITE:\nhttp://www.mamashomerome.com</string>
    <string name="mamas_home_description">ABOUT:\n4 Star Hotel - Mama\'s Home Rome overlooks the Campo
        de\' Fiori square.  This upscale all-suite hotel in a 14th-century home is an 8-minute walk
        from the ancient Pantheon temple, 1 km from the 2nd-century Castel Sant\'Angelo and 2 km from
        the Colosseum. Chic suites with sleek decor and wood ceiling beams have free Wi-Fi,
        flat-screen TVs and Nespresso machines; some feature in-room, claw-foot tubs. Upgraded suites
        offer views of the square. Bike rentals are available, as is chauffeur service from the airport
        or train station for a fee.</string>
    <string name="rome_life_hotel_name">Rome Life Hotel</string>
    <string name="rome_life_hotel_address">ADDRESS:\nVia Palermo, 10, 00184 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="rome_life_hotel_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 9929 1210</string>
    <string name="rome_life_hotel_website">WEBSITE:\nhttp://www.romelifehotel.com</string>
    <string name="rome_life_hotel_description">ABOUT:\n4 Star Hotel - Rome Life Hotel is a chic downtown hotel
        with a wooden facade. It\'s an 8-minute walk from a metro stop and 1.3 km from the Colosseum.  The
        upscale, modern rooms include free Wi-Fi, 107-cm flat-screen HDTVs with satellite channels,
        minibars, and tea and coffeemakers. The hotel serves a complimentary breakfast buffet in a
        contemporary dining room. There\'s a similarly styled bar and a 24/7 front desk.</string>
    <string name="inn_at_roman_forum_name">The Inn at the Roman Forum</string>
    <string name="inn_at_roman_forum_address">ADDRESS:\nVia degli Ibernesi, 30, 00184 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="inn_at_roman_forum_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 6919 0970</string>
    <string name="inn_at_roman_forum_website">WEBSITE:\nhttp://www.theinnattheromanforum.com</string>
    <string name="inn_at_roman_forum_description">ABOUT:\n5 Star Hotel - The Inn at the Roman Forum is a
        4-minute walk from the bus station, this upscale urban hotel with Roman ruins and an annex is
        also 12 minutes from the Colosseum. The plush, elegant rooms offer free Wi-Fi, flat-screen
        TVs and iPod docks, plus minibars. Upgraded rooms have Jacuzzis. Some have fireplaces or
        sitting areas, and suites including sitting rooms. Upgraded suites have patios with rooftop
        access.  Other amenities include a business center, a lounge with a fireplace, and an ancient
        crypt with 2000-year-old stone engravings.</string>
    <string name="hotel_raphael_name">Hotel Raphaël</string>
    <string name="hotel_raphael_address">ADDRESS:\nLargo Febo, 2, 00186 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="hotel_raphael_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 682831</string>
    <string name="hotel_raphael_website">WEBSITE:\nhttp://www.raphaelhotel.com</string>
    <string name="hotel_raphael_description">ABOUT:\n5 Star Hotel - Hotel Raphaël is a 2-minute walk from the
        1st-century Piazza Navona and the bus station. This sophisticated, ivy-covered hotel is a 14-minute
        walk from the famous Trevi Fountain. The warmly decorated, upscale rooms offer free Wi-Fi,
        flat-screen TVs and minibars. Some of the upgraded rooms have terraces, and elegant suites
        include living rooms. Some have private balconies. There\'s a refined restaurant with seasonal
        outdoor seating, plus an on-site museum and an art gallery.</string>
    <string name="nh_collection_cinquecento_name">NH Collection Roma Palazzo Cinquecento</string>
    <string name="nh_collection_cinquecento_address">ADDRESS:\nPiazza dei Cinquecento, 90, 00185 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="nh_collection_cinquecento_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 492221</string>
    <string name="nh_collection_cinquecento_website">WEBSITE:\nhttps://www.nh-hotels.com/hotel/nh-collection
        -roma-palazzo-cinquecento?gmb=new</string>
    <string name="nh_collection_cinquecento_description">ABOUT:\n5 Star Hotel - NH Collection Roma Palazzo
        Cinquecento overlooks Piazza dei Cinquecento and adjacent to Roma Termini train station. This
        upmarket hotel fronted by a garden with Roman ruins is 2 km from the Colosseum. The contemporary
        rooms come with free Wi-Fi and flat-screen TVs, plus minibars, espresso machines and rainfall
        showers. Upgraded quarters provide sitting areas and/or terraces, while suites offer separate
        living areas with sofabeds.</string>
    <string name="pantheon_caesar_relais_name">Pantheon Caesar Relais</string>
    <string name="pantheon_caesar_relais_address">ADDRESS:\nVicolo di S. Nicola de\' Cesarini, 2, 00148
        Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="pantheon_caesar_relais_phone">PHONE:\n+39 06 6880 5850</string>
    <string name="pantheon_caesar_relais_website">WEBSITE:\nhttps://www.pantheoncaesarrelais.it</string>
    <string name="pantheon_caesar_relais_description">ABOUT:\n5 Star Hotel - Pantheon Caesar Relais is on a
        cobbled street opposite the Largo di Torre Argentina archaeological site. This relaxed
        bed-and-breakfast is a 5-minute walk from the iconic Pantheon church, a 9-minute walk from
        Piazza Navona square and 3 km from Roma Termini train station. The 5 straightforward rooms
        provide complimentary Wi-Fi, flat-screen TVs and minifridges, plus tea and coffeemakers;
        most offer Largo di Torre Argentina views. Distinctive features in individual rooms include
        a balcony and a sitting area. Continental breakfast is served in-room.</string>
    <string name="walk_on_walk_off_rome_name">Walk On Walk Off: Flexible Rome Tour Pass</string>
    <string name="walk_on_walk_off_rome_duration">DURATION:\n1 hour</string>
    <string name="walk_on_walk_off_rome_cost">COST:\nfrom $71.37 USD</string>
    <string name="walk_on_walk_off_rome_booking">BOOK IT:\nhttps://www.walksofitaly.com/rome-tours/walk
        -on-walk-off-rome-tour-pass</string>
    <string name="walk_on_walk_off_rome_description">ABOUT:\nUnlock Rome with a flexible tour pass allowing
        you to take tours on your own schedule. Choose from 10 different tours, from relaxed city strolls,
        to deep dives into history and even a food tour. Don\'t worry about reserving in advance. Just
        show up 10 minutes before a tour starts and walk on. If your plans change, it\'s not a problem,
        the tour runs with or without you.</string>
    <string name="top_tier_colosseum_name">Top Tier Colosseum Tour with Special Access to 3rd, 4th
        and 5th Levels, Roman Forum and Palatine Hill</string>
    <string name="top_tier_colosseum_duration">DURATION:\n3 hours 30 minutes</string>
    <string name="top_tier_colosseum_cost">COST:\nfrom $102.82 USD</string>
    <string name="top_tier_colosseum_booking">BOOK IT:\nhttps://www.walksofitaly.com/rome-tours/top-
        level-colosseum-tour</string>
    <string name="top_tier_colosseum_description">ABOUT:\nStep up into the 3rd, 4th and 5th tiers of the Colosseum
        for spectacular views. Enjoy a full general-access Colosseum tour with an expert guide.
        Immerse yourself in the daily life of ancient Romans in the Roman Forum and Palatine Hill.</string>
    <string name="rome_in_a_day_name">Rome In A Day Tour: Including Vatican, Colosseum and Historic Center</string>
    <string name="rome_in_a_day_duration">DURATION:\n7 hours 30 minutes (1 hour 15 minute break)</string>
    <string name="rome_in_a_day_cost">COST:\nfrom $156.04 USD</string>
    <string name="rome_in_a_day_booking">BOOK IT:\nhttps://www.walksofitaly.com/rome-tours/rome-in-a-day-tour</string>
    <string name="rome_in_a_day_description">ABOUT:\nRome wasn\'t built in a day, but with our tour, you
        can see it in a day! You will see all the top sights of Rome including the Vatican Museums, Colosseum
        and historic center (Pantheon, Trevi Fountain and Piazza Navona). Also includes a self-guided
        visit to St. Peter\'s Basilica. With a private transfer from the historic center to the Vatican,
        we\'ve taken care of all the details for a fun, hassle-free day. Enjoy skip the line entrance at
        all the sites you visit (Vatican, Colosseum, St Peter\'s Basilica).</string>
    <string name="pompeii_amalfi_coast_name">Pompeii Tour from Rome with Amalfi Coast Drive</string>
    <string name="pompeii_amalfi_coast_duration">DURATION:\n13 hours (approx.)</string>
    <string name="pompeii_amalfi_coast_cost">COST:\nfrom $216.52 USD</string>
    <string name="pompeii_amalfi_coast_booking">BOOK IT:\nhttps://www.walksofitaly.com/rome-tours/pompeii
        -tours-from-rome</string>
    <string name="pompeii_amalfi_coast_description">ABOUT:\nExplore incredible archaeological sites at Pompeii
        with an expert guide. Relax and enjoy a drive along the Amalfi Coast with a stop at Positano
        town. Round-trip transport and a friendly English-speaking tour leader make this a fun and
        hassle free tour.</string>
    <string name="crypts_catacombs_name">Crypts, Bones and Catacombs: An Underground Tour of Rome</string>
    <string name="crypts_catacombs_duration">DURATION:\n3 hours</string>
    <string name="crypts_catacombs_cost">COST:\nfrom $83.46 USD</string>
    <string name="crypts_catacombs_booking">BOOK IT:\nhttps://www.walksofitaly.com/rome-tours/rome-catacombs-tour</string>
    <string name="crypts_catacombs_description">ABOUT:\nVisit the quietest and most impressive of Rome\'s Catacombs
        in a small group - so you can hear your guide! See it for yourself: The eerie \"Bone Chapel\",
        covered in the bones of 4,000 friars. Discover just how deep the history of Rome goes at a
        multi-layered (multi-purpose!) Ancient Roman temple/prison/Basilica.</string>
    <string name="ghost_mystery_walk_name">Rome Ghost and Mystery Night Walking Tour</string>
    <string name="ghost_mystery_walk_duration">DURATION:\n1 hour 30 minutes</string>
    <string name="ghost_mystery_walk_cost">COST:\nfrom $29.35 USD</string>
    <string name="ghost_mystery_walk_booking">BOOK IT:\nhttps://citywonders.com/rome-tours/rome-ghost-tour</string>
    <string name="ghost_mystery_walk_description">ABOUT:\nAs the sun sets over Rome a new city comes to light
        – a city of legends and mystery, where thousands of years have left a story behind every stone.
        The stories Rome has to tell are far from the average bedtime tale, fraught with murder, execution
        and haunting. Join our expert, English-speaking storytellers who will tell you about the unseen
        history behind the stunning buildings of central Rome. You\’ll see the house of the most notorious
        (and empathetic) murderer ever to work in the Eternal City and how Rome cured its crime problems
        by hanging pictures of the Virgin Mary on every corner. and visit the bridge that legend has it,
        is haunted by the ghost of the female Pope.</string>
    <string name="vip_colosseum_forum_name">VIP Colosseum Underground Tour with Roman Forum and Palatine Hill</string>
    <string name="vip_colosseum_forum_duration">DURATION:\n3 hours 45 minutes</string>
    <string name="vip_colosseum_forum_cost">COST:\nfrom $114.91 USD</string>
    <string name="vip_colosseum_forum_booking">BOOK IT:\nhttps://www.walksofitaly.com/rome-tours/colosseum
        -underground-tours</string>
    <string name="vip_colosseum_forum_description">ABOUT:\nGo where few tourists have gone before with this VIP
        Colosseum Underground tour, taking you to closed areas of the Colosseum so you can truly experience
        the magic of Ancient Rome. Visit the Colosseum underground and walk on the arena floor. Enjoy a
        full tour of the general access areas of the Colosseum, Roman Forum and Palatine Hill.</string>
    <string name="skip_line_vatican_name">Skip the Line: Vatican Museums, Sistine Chapel and St Peter\'s
        Basilica Half-Day Walking Tour</string>
    <string name="skip_line_vatican_duration">DURATION:\n3 hours (approx.)</string>
    <string name="skip_line_vatican_cost">COST:\nfrom $44.27 USD</string>
    <string name="skip_line_vatican_booking">BOOK IT:\nhttps://www.viator.com/tours/Rome/Skip-the-Line-Vatican-Museums
        -Sistine-Chapel-and-St-Peters-Basilica-Half-Day-Walking-Tour/d511-3058VATICAN</string>
    <string name="skip_line_vatican_description">ABOUT:\nDiscover Vatican City with a guide and skip-the-line
        access, including the Vatican Museums, St Peter\’s Basilica and the Sistine Chapel. Home to the
        world\’s largest private portfolio of artwork, the Vatican is a must-see for visitors to Rome,
        and the best way to explore it is with a guide. Learn about Raphael\’s Rooms, the Michelangelo
        frescoes of the Sistine Chapel, the "La Pietà" sculpture in St Peter\’s Basilica and more.
        Choose from several start times or upgrade to a small-group tour with just 12 people.\n
        *The entrance fee (not included) is payable on the day of your tour.</string>
    <string name="colosseum_ancient_rome_by_night_name">Colosseum and Ancient Rome Tour by Night</string>
    <string name="colosseum_ancient_rome_by_night_duration">DURATION:\n2 hours 30 minutes (approx.)</string>
    <string name="colosseum_ancient_rome_by_night_cost">COST:\nfrom $94.53 USD</string>
    <string name="colosseum_ancient_rome_by_night_booking">BOOK IT:\nhttps://www.viator.com/tours/Rome/
        Colosseum-and-Ancient-Rome-Tour-by-Night/d511-3731COLOSSEUMNIGHT</string>
    <string name="colosseum_ancient_rome_by_night_description">ABOUT:\nTour the amphitheater and other sites
        of Ancient Rome under the atmospheric cover of darkness during this 2.5-hour evening tour.
        Learn about the ruins of the Roman Forum seen from the Piazza del Campidoglio, and enter the
        Colosseum after the daytime crowds have disappeared and the temperature has dropped. Visit
        the arena\’s underground chambers, which are closed to most of the public, and stand where
        gladiators once stood centuries ago. This tour is limited to 25 people.</string>
    <string name="gladiator_school_name">Roman Gladiator School: Learn How to Become a Gladiator</string>
    <string name="gladiator_school_duration">DURATION:\n2 hours (approx.)</string>
    <string name="gladiator_school_cost">COST:\nfrom $65.81 USD</string>
    <string name="gladiator_school_booking">BOOK IT:\nhttps://www.viator.com/tours/Rome/Roman-Gladiator
        -School-Learn-How-to-Become-a-Gladiator/d511-2466GLAD</string>
    <string name="gladiator_school_description">ABOUT:\nFind out what it takes to be an ancient Roman gladiator
        at the Gladiator School of Rome. During a hands-on lesson with instructors from the Historic
        Group of Rome, learn how to fight with authentic weapons of the time while wearing a traditional
        gladiator tunic and belt. Located on the Appian Way, not far from the Colosseum, this class is
        a unique and interactive way to learn about ancient Roman history, sports, and culture.\n
        *Select a lesson time when booking.</string>
</resources>